<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<xliff xmlns="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="1.2" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2 xliff-core-1.2-transitional.xsd">
  <file datatype="xml" original="ns-System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement.xml" source-language="en-US" target-language="de-DE">
    <header>
      <tool tool-id="mdxliff" tool-name="mdxliff" tool-version="1.0-efd8310" tool-company="Microsoft" />
      <xliffext:skl_file_name xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">5a83ea4b-dd12-480b-bfc8-267272ef1864fefc91ccc5056e6a3e0640141b2ea2b1dffd83da.skl</xliffext:skl_file_name>
      <xliffext:version xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">1.2</xliffext:version>
      <xliffext:ms.openlocfilehash xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">fefc91ccc5056e6a3e0640141b2ea2b1dffd83da</xliffext:ms.openlocfilehash>
      <xliffext:ms.sourcegitcommit xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">df6cf590aa3087f6c7c202712eee781c6a3c8f96</xliffext:ms.sourcegitcommit>
      <xliffext:ms.lasthandoff xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">05/10/2018</xliffext:ms.lasthandoff>
    </header>
    <body>
      <group id="content" extype="content">
        <trans-unit id="101" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve">
          <source>The <ph id="ph1">&lt;see cref="N:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement" /&gt;</ph> namespace provides uniform access and manipulation of user, computer, and group security principals across the multiple principal stores: Active Directory Domain Services (AD DS), Active Directory Lightweight Directory Services (AD LDS), and Machine SAM (MSAM).</source>
          <target state="translated">Der <ph id="ph1">&lt;see cref="N:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement" /&gt;</ph>-Namespace ermöglicht den einheitlichen Zugriff und die einheitliche Bearbeitung von Sicherheitsprinzipalen für Benutzer, Computer und Gruppen im Hinblick auf die verschiedenen Prinzipalspeicher: Active Directory-Domänendienste (AD DS), Active Directory-Lightweight-Verzeichnisdienste (AD LDS) und Computer-SAM (MSAM).</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="102" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve">
          <source><ph id="ph1">&lt;see cref="N:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement" /&gt;</ph> manages directory objects independent of the <ph id="ph2">&lt;see cref="N:System.DirectoryServices" /&gt;</ph> namespace.</source>
          <target state="translated"><ph id="ph1">&lt;see cref="N:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement" /&gt;</ph> verwaltet Verzeichnisobjekte, die vom <ph id="ph2">&lt;see cref="N:System.DirectoryServices" /&gt;</ph>-Namespace unabhängig sind.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="103" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Managed directory services applications can take advantage of the <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement&gt;</ph> API to simplify management of user, computer and group principals.</source>
          <target state="translated">Verwaltete Verzeichnisdienste nutzen die <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement&gt;</ph> API zum Vereinfachen der Verwaltung von Benutzer-, Computer und Prinzipalen.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="104" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Solutions that previously required intricate knowledge of the store or lengthy code, such as finding all groups to which a user belongs, are accomplished in a few lines of code with the <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement&gt;</ph> API.</source>
          <target state="translated">Lösungen, die zuvor umfassende Kenntnisse des Speichers oder langen Code erforderlichen, z. B. Suchen aller Gruppen, denen ein Benutzer angehört, werden mit wenigen Codezeilen erreicht die <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement&gt;</ph> API.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="105" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>The following features are available on the <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement&gt;</ph> API:</source>
          <target state="translated">Die folgenden Funktionen sind verfügbar, auf die <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement&gt;</ph> API:</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="106" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Basic directory operations such as creating and updating security principals is simplified.</source>
          <target state="translated">Grundlegende Verzeichnisvorgänge wie das Erstellen und Aktualisieren von Sicherheitsprinzipalen wurde vereinfacht.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="107" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>The application requires less knowledge of the underlying stores to perform these operations.</source>
          <target state="translated">Die Anwendung erfordert weniger Kenntnisse der zugrunde liegenden Speicher zum Ausführen dieser Vorgänge.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="108" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Applications can extend the object model to include new types of directory objects.</source>
          <target state="translated">Anwendungen können das Objektmodell, um neue Typen von Verzeichnisobjekten aufzunehmen erweitern.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="109" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Account management tasks, such as enabling and disabling a user account, are simplified.</source>
          <target state="translated">Konto-Verwaltungsaufgaben, z. B. das Aktivieren und Deaktivieren eines Benutzerkontos vereinfacht werden.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="110" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Cross-store support allows group objects in the Active Directory Domain Services (AD DS), Active Directory Lightweight Directory Services (AD LDS), and Machine SAM (MSAM) databases to contain members from different types of stores.</source>
          <target state="translated">Cross-Store-Unterstützung können Gruppenobjekte in Active Directory-Domänendienste (AD DS), Active Directory Lightweight Directory Services (AD LDS) und Computer SAM (MSAM)-Datenbanken Member aus verschiedenen Typen von Geschäften enthalten.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="111" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Query by example searching, available on the <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement.PrincipalSearcher&gt;</ph> class, enables applications to set properties on a principal object and search the selected store for other objects that contain matching property values.</source>
          <target state="translated">Abfrage durch das Beispiel zu suchen, auf die <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement.PrincipalSearcher&gt;</ph> Klasse, ermöglicht Anwendungen legen Sie Eigenschaften für ein Hauptobjekt, und suchen Sie im ausgewählten Store andere Objekte, die entsprechenden Eigenschaftswerte enthalten.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="112" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Enhanced search on computer, user and group principal objects enables applications to search the selected store for matching principal objects.</source>
          <target state="translated">Erweiterte Suche auf Computer, Benutzer und Gruppe principal-Objekten ermöglicht Anwendungen, den ausgewählten Store für den Abgleich von principal-Objekte gesucht werden soll.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="113" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Recursive search, available on the group principal object, enables applications to search a group recursively and return only principal objects that are leaf nodes.</source>
          <target state="translated">Rekursive Suche an, auf das Gruppenprinzipalobjekt, kann Anwendungen einen Gruppe rekursiv zu suchen und nur principal-Objekte, die Blattknoten sind zurückgeben.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="114" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Credential validation against the Machine SAM, AD DS, and AD LS stores is simplified.</source>
          <target state="translated">Überprüfung der Anmeldeinformationen für die Computer-SAM, AD DS und AD LS-Speicher wurde vereinfacht.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="115" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Connections speeds are increased by using the Fast Concurrent Bind (FSB) feature when available.</source>
          <target state="translated">Mindestgeschwindigkeiten für die Verbindungen werden erhöht, mithilfe der Funktion schnelle gleichzeitige binden (FSB), falls verfügbar.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="116" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Connection caching decreases the number of ports used.</source>
          <target state="translated">Verbindung Zwischenspeichern verringert die Anzahl der verwendeten Ports.</target>       </trans-unit>
      </group>
    </body>
  </file>
</xliff>